GOROGORI CHANNEL GOGO!
Yay!
It's outside.
Yes, I mean outside.
Well, today...
Misaki has successfully become the King of Monsters!
Then perhaps...
Yes, let's go together.
Great!
Yay!
I've become the King of Specters!
I've become the king of monsters, which means we have a date together today, as promised.
Thank you very much.
I've been hearing a lot of people asking me if it's ready yet, and I've been looking forward to it, so I'm going to have fun today.
I'm sorry to say, but I'm actually doing the same thing as Kirakura again for the opening at night.
I was having a little too much fun, and when I realized it, it was already nighttime.
But I'm sure everyone will watch the video, so please enjoy it. Bye bye.
First of all, we are going to eat shaved ice.
Here you go.
I ordered a certain thing.
Um~~ Anon babies
They won't fall over! They won't fall over!
Harusato Miyuruhanded
haritana jiele actively
I heard that you have prepared it by any chance.
jun mucho gracias
Wait, this size grass TWO JEOPSONES
I'm going to be gone.
Awww.
и
Thank you for watching!
Really.
A little bit.
A little bit...
I don't know.
I'll do my best.
How is it?
Delicious.
It's a real peach.
This is some kind of cream.
It's delicious.
You know, I've got a question for you guys.
I've been seeing a lot of this lately.
Are you Yohka?
Kira? You know...
There's so many of them.
What should I do?
I'll teach you a trick.
I do it all the time.
I don't know... when I hear you talk about this...
If you come to me and say...
"Are you Yo-kasai? Say, "Are you Yosaka?
You can only say it yourself.
Thank you very much.
There's a video of you.
Your face.
I went a little low key today.
I've always had a lot of it.
I don't think so.
Maybe not.
Keep doing it.
I get it.
Why does everyone else eat it?
All of them.
Which one eats which one?
We eat in together.
We eat in together
I'll eat with you.
Ta-da!
Pitta me.
Make it fit.
Ready?
It's really good.
Yum! Yum! Yum!
I'll take you out
Next store
Soy Soft & Fried Donuts
Please
Ghetto
Then let's eat somewhere else.
After you.
Go ahead.
Soy donuts.
Okay, you can eat first.
All right.
Keep going. Wait. Keep going.
Okay. - Okay.
Yes, sir.
Pull!
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
A few more.
Worst.
Let's go get one.
This is just regular soft serve ice cream.
I think it's soya.
Soy?
Because it's called "Soy Soft & Fried Donuts.
I see.
It's good. I recommend it.
Yeah!
It's kind of...
Yeah! Yeah!
Yeah!
It's good.
It's not working.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Ponies.
No, but, you know, I like it when you do that when you move.
I like it when you do that. You're so relaxed.
It's like, "This, this is Yohka.
I don't know, right?
You're really putting yourself on the line.
I was a one-time Yo-hwa.
Yes, Yokka for a time, Yokka as a PG student
I know, right?
So cute!
Kitsu!
I want a uniform.
Hey, this is kinda cute.
I think I'd like it.
Just a little bit.
Clean it up.
Cute.
Super.
Mmm.
mmm
It's a little big.
It's very tasty in terms of color
There you go.
Ta-da!
Glamper.
Glampers.
What's glamper?
Grampa.
Yes, sir.
Then I'll wear it as a sign of respect for you, Grandpa.
I'll wear it as a sign of respect.
Yes, sir.
Here we are!
Ta-da!
Here we go.
yazurisch
4 and raw yuan
Thank you for your time
Thank you for watching!
Yes, so we had a fun date for a day!
We went shopping together.
We shopped together for clothes and stuff.
We ate a lot of food and now we have to work again. Please continue to watch the Galgal Channel.
Please watch the Galgal Channel. That's all.
I'm sorry.
Well...